In British Columbia students are expected to meet
在不列颠哥伦比亚省的学生需要达到一定的标准
certain criteria in order to meet Ministry of Education requirements.
以满足教育部的毕业要求。
Here at Bodwell high school, we work closely with students
在博域中学，我们紧密帮助学生
To help them follow through with their graduation plan
来他们完成毕业计划。
Take a look at this.
让我们来看一下这个…
This graduation plan can be found on our website.
您可以在我们的网站上找到这个毕业计划。
There are six main components to our graduation program,
我们的毕业计划有六个主要组成部分:
the first being "communication".
第一个是“沟通”。
We have relevant up-to-date communication
我们确保与学生之间保持最新的相应沟通
between staff and students, which is imperative for student success.
这是学生成功的必要条件。
We use email personalized notifications, one-on-one and  group meetings, online grading program
我们使用个人电子邮件通知、一对一或小组会议、网上评分程序、
"my blueprint" software, daily announcements, and bulletin boards
“我的蓝图”软件、每日公告、和学校公告栏向我们的学生传达必要的信息。
The second component is "graduation requirements".
第二部分是“毕业要求”。
Our counselors individually explore.graduation requirements with students.
我们的辅导老师与学生一对一地探索毕业要求，
They ensure that students have completed the 80 credits needed
他们确保学生完成所需的80个学分以取得BC省的高中文凭。
We offer a wide variety of grade 10, 11, and 12 courses
我们提供各种10,11和12年级的课程，
including Advanced Placement calculus, Studio Art, Physics, and Mandarin.
包括大学先修微积分、工作室美术、物理和普通话等等。
Over 30 after-school clubs and 40 Saturday enrichment courses
我们学校有30多个课后兴趣会社和40个周六兴趣加强课程，
are offered to help students supplement their learning and enrich their post-secondary applications.
来帮助学生补充他们的学习和加强他们大学申请的竞争力。
The third component is "provincial exams". The previous provincial exams are being replaced
第三部分是“省试”。
They are offered in January, June, and August of each year.
这两个评估在每年的一月，六月和八月进行。
In addition to classroom instruction,
除了课堂教学之外，
students will be given numerous opportunities to prepare for those two assessments
通过课后学术会社和额外考试练习，
via academic clubs and extra practice sessions that are offered after school.
学生有很多机会为这两项评估做准备。
The fourth component is "English proficiency".
第四部分是“英语应用水平”。
We assist students by offering IELTS enrichment courses
我们通过在周六提供雅思课程来帮助学生。
The fifth "career life connections and career life education".
第五部分是“职业生涯联系”和”职业生涯教育” 。
Before students graduate students they must complete two academic courses:
在学生毕业之前，他们必须完成这两门学术课程：
career life connections and career life education.
职业生涯联系和职业生涯教育
that are designed to help students prepare to be lifelong learners
这两们课是旨在帮助学生成为终身学习者，
These are components that are essential to balanced physical and mental health.
这些是对平衡身心健康至关重要的组成部分。
Students will be expected to do at least 30 hours
学生至少要完成30个小时的志愿服务，
of volunteer experience and successfully produce a capstone project.
并成功地制作了一个研究项目。
The sixth component is the post-secondary plan.
第六部分是高中毕业后的计划。
we offer a rich support program for post-secondary applications.
我们为学生的大学申请提供丰富的支持计划。
When a student graduates from Bodwell high school they can feel confident
当一名学生从博域中学毕业，他们可以自信地说，
they have received the individualized support
他们已经获得了个別化的支持，
for their post-secondary endeavours
来为他们高中之后的学习做准备。